[{"ne000683":{"desc":"","pattern":"earth","type":"LOC","words":1},"ne000889":{"desc":"","pattern":"Genius","type":"PER","words":1},"ne001517":{"desc":"In Greek and Roman mythology, each of nine goddesses, the daughters of Zeus and Mnemosyne, who preside over the arts and sciences. The Muses are generally listed as Calliope (epic poetry), Clio (history), Euterpe (flute playing and lyric poetry), Terpsichore (choral dancing and song), Erato (lyre playing and lyric poetry), Melpomene (tragedy), Thalia (comedy and light verse), Polyhymnia (hymns, and later mime), and Urania (astronomy).","pattern":"Muse","type":"PER","words":1},"ne001518":{"desc":"In Greek and Roman mythology, each of nine goddesses, the daughters of Zeus and Mnemosyne, who preside over the arts and sciences. The Muses are generally listed as Calliope (epic poetry), Clio (history), Euterpe (flute playing and lyric poetry), Terpsichore (choral dancing and song), Erato (lyre playing and lyric poetry), Melpomene (tragedy), Thalia (comedy and light verse), Polyhymnia (hymns, and later mime), and Urania (astronomy).","pattern":"Muses","type":"PER","words":1},"ne001531":{"desc":"","pattern":"Narcissa","type":"PER","words":1},"ne001617":{"desc":"","pattern":"Orinda","type":"PER","words":1},"ne001666":{"desc":"","pattern":"Paphos","type":"LOC","words":1},"ne001788":{"desc":"","pattern":"Plato","type":"PER","words":1},"ne002337":{"desc":"","pattern":"Urania","type":"PER","words":1},"ne002456":{"desc":"","pattern":"Angel","type":"PER","words":1},"nea00499":{"desc":"","pattern":"Plantane","type":"MSC","words":1}},{"ne-o4984-364660-1":{"id":"ne001531","loc":{"line":"o4984-l18435","words":"o4984-364660"},"mech":"comp-gaz","occur":"ne-o4984-364660-1","resp":"#AH"},"ne-o4984-364880-1":{"id":"ne001517","loc":{"line":"o4984-l18445","words":"o4984-364880"},"mech":"comp-gaz","occur":"ne-o4984-364880-1","resp":"#AH"},"ne-o4984-365190-1":{"id":"ne001617","loc":{"line":"o4984-l18465","words":"o4984-365190"},"mech":"comp-gaz","occur":"ne-o4984-365190-1","resp":"#AH"},"ne-o4984-365300-1":{"id":"ne000889","loc":{"line":"o4984-l18470","words":"o4984-365300"},"mech":"comp-gaz","occur":"ne-o4984-365300-1","resp":"#AH"},"ne-o4984-366100-1":{"id":"ne002337","loc":{"line":"o4984-l18520","words":"o4984-366100"},"mech":"comp-gaz","occur":"ne-o4984-366100-1","resp":"#AH"},"ne-o4984-366600-1":{"id":"ne001666","loc":{"line":"o4984-l18525","words":"o4984-366600"},"mech":"comp-gaz","occur":"ne-o4984-366600-1","resp":"#AH"},"ne-o4984-367570-1":{"id":"ne000683","loc":{"line":"o4984-l18580","words":"o4984-367570"},"mech":"comp-gaz","occur":"ne-o4984-367570-1","resp":"#AH"},"ne-o4984-367690-1":{"id":"ne001666","loc":{"line":"o4984-l18585","words":"o4984-367690"},"mech":"comp-gaz","occur":"ne-o4984-367690-1","resp":"#AH"},"ne-o4984-368050-1":{"id":"ne002456","loc":{"line":"o4984-l18605","words":"o4984-368050"},"mech":"comp-gaz","occur":"ne-o4984-368050-1","resp":"#AH"},"ne-o4984-368630-1":{"id":"ne001788","loc":{"line":"o4984-l18640","words":"o4984-368630"},"mech":"comp-gaz","occur":"ne-o4984-368630-1","resp":"#AH"},"ne-o4984-368690-1":{"id":"ne001518","loc":{"line":"o4984-l18645","words":"o4984-368690"},"mech":"comp-gaz","occur":"ne-o4984-368690-1","resp":"#AH"},"ne-o4984-369400-1":{"id":"nea00499","loc":{"line":"o4984-l18665","words":"o4984-369400"},"mech":"comp-pos","occur":"ne-o4984-369400-1","resp":"#AH"}}]